Harumotoya
So you want to know
where Yuki's little sister is?
I have no idea, for the record.
No fair only admitting that
after I bought you ramen!
Simply asking me for information
is worth at least that much.
The only leads you have are that bell
and that her name is "Hua," right?
I'll put in exactly one bowl of ramen's
worth of effort, so... don't mind if I do!
Also, what kind of teacher
makes a student pay for their—
Don't distract me when
I'm getting my ramen on. 'Kay?
Oh, man. Japanese noodles sure taste
different when they're the real deal.
So much better than sushi!
This is probably 80% of the reason
why I'm still in Japan.
That much?!
Yuki, you get where I'm coming from, right?
Y-You... Y-You... Y-You...
Stop looking so happy!
I knew you loved this
Katsuda's Sauce stuff, but...
I didn't know you carried around
your own personal supply.
It's like how some people get extra garlic,
right? Ms. Yuki has hers with extra sauce.
Apologize to the ramen, damn it!
If you want the information,
go without the sauce next time!
Otherwise, no deal!
There's only a little bit of sauce left...
Katsuda Side Dish Store
Oh, I'm sorry.
Episode 8: The Autumn With You and the Sauce.
We're all sold out of the sauce.
The students have been buying it up, you see.
Oh, that's right!
The Katsuda Festival's coming up, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Ms. Maid.
Around this time of the year,
it's hard to make enough to meet demand.
We have a lot of back orders, too,
so you'll need to wait about a week
before you can buy more.
One whole week...
Sorry 'bout that.
Oh, no... Thank you for always
making your delicious s-sauce...
This is the most character development
I've seen from her yet!
Hm... Yeah, it's gonna be tough
making this much last a whole week.
I will cherish... every drop...
I need to think of some way to cheer her up.
Oh, come to think of it!
If you met your little sister again,
what would you want to talk to her about?
My memories of my childhood are vague.
Even my sister's face is hazy,
and I only remember fragments of my parents.
I was all alone before I even
knew what was happening.
But I remember this bell.
My mother gave one to both of us.
I thought maybe my sister would
find me if I held onto it...
but nothing so miraculous
has happened over these past ten years.
Besides, I'm actually scared to meet her.
It may be that my little sister
holds a grudge against me.
Oh, no... Did I do the wrong thing
asking Grace for help?
No, not at all.
Even if we don't meet, just knowing that
my little sister is safe would make me happy.
I see...
I tried to console her, but she
ended up reassuring me instead...
S'up?!
Yuki, you have a little sister?
I bet she's as beautiful as you are!
Taiga?! Kobachi!
What are you two doing here?
Hey, now, do I need to remind you that
Nazca's new album dropped today?
On top of that...
Feast your eyes on this autographed
limited edition I won in a lottery!
It's god-tier! Thank you, world!
Isn't Nazca that singer who's
attending the Katsuda Festival?
Yeah!
You guys shopping?
You two sure are close.
Huh?
Not to mention, you've had a lot of
relatives suddenly show up lately.
Don't you think it's all a bit much?
What can I say? It's a coincidence.
While we, your dear friends,
are thrown aside...
Come on, Kobachi, it's all right.
Don't be jealous.
If anything, I'm grateful to you, Yuki.
Ever since you showed up, Hitoyoshi
seems like he's been having lots of fun.
Master Hitoyoshi has?
You bet! He was a real mess
during middle school, y'know.
Only we know what he was like then.
Hey, hold up!
He was rebelling against his dad
and going through his edgy phase,
and man, he sure was a handful.
"Edgy phase"?
Remember how he'd always wear a black
trench coat, even in the middle of summer?
Chocolate
He called himself "The Angry Knife"!
"The Angry Knife"...
It's so embarrassing to have this come out now
after Ms. Yuki's actual dark past...
Do you know why he stopped cleaning
the house in the first place?
It wasn't that he didn't know how,
he was just such a brat that—
Taiga! If you say one more
word, I'll make you pay!
Oh, no! My autographed CD!
Katsuda's Sauce
Katsuda's
Sauce
FIN
That night...
Katsuda's Sauce
That hurt... I can't believe
you'd treat me that way...
I-I'm sorry...
I don't think I can let you lick me anymore.
Ms. Yuki, can I come in?
Y-Yes, feel free.
Oh, did you just wake up?
It's almost lunchtime.
K-Katsuda's Sauce hates me now.
I'm done for.
There's no point in living anymore.
All right. Tell me what happened.
I see... Katsuda's Sauce
spoke to you in your dreams.
Don't worry about it too much.
You'll be able to buy more next week.
Yes... That may be so,
but that's not the only thing I dreamt of.
What? You have other scary dreams?
No...
The next day...
I-I'm sorry...
And the day after that...
Yes?
C-Could you please sleep next to me?
What?
A-A distress signal?!
I'm scared to sleep, and...
I'm scared that I can't sleep...
P-Putting sleeping arrangements aside for now,
I already know I'm going to be up late
cramming for the test tomorrow,
so I guess we could talk
until you feel ready to sleep?
Could you please do that for me?
O-Okay.
Master Hitoyoshi,
you are very kind, and the people
around you care for you dearly.
You are a very personable person.
Huh? What's all this all of a sudden?!
That's not true...
Um... Master Hitoyoshi...
Have you ever felt hatred toward anyone?
Do I hate anyone?
Hate, huh... Dunno if I've ever felt strongly
enough about anyone to call it hate, but...
If I had to choose, it'd probably be...
my dad, I think.
Your father?
It's not that I hate him exactly, but...
Lots of things happened in the past,
and that's why I'm keeping
my distance, in a way.
It's just something that
comes with being family.
Something that comes with being family...
I hate you, Sis!
Ms. Yuki?
Um, I think I'll return to my room, so as not
to interfere with your studies any further.
Oh? Are you sure?
Katsuda's Sauce
It's all your fault, you know.
All of it.
You threw me away, just like you
threw your little sister away.
You only know how to kill people,
and that's why everyone hates you.
That's not true... I'm doing my best...
I'm trying to be a normal—
Even now, you're causing trouble
for Hitoyoshi and the others.
Take a look.
He doesn't really want to be with you.
Everything that's happened has been your fault.
How old are you, Maria?
I turn seven next month on the 25th.
I heard you can speak 15 languages.
Yes! I learned them so I could help my mom.
When you were young, you were a prodigy.
It seems your mother works as an interpreter.
Yes!
My goodness, Maria, you're answering
all of the questions so well.
Is this also something
you learned from your mother?
Yes, I did!
My mom is beautiful and smart,
and she has a wonderful smile!
Your observational skills were superb,
you had a photographic memory,
and your athletic ability was
far beyond that of a child.
You were in the spotlight,
but you lacked interest in
your talents or the attention.
The only things you had eyes for were...
Mom! Dad!
the smiles on your beloved parents' faces.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, Maria!
There's some on your face.
Do we have guests?
I'll check it out.
I will, too. You girls keep eating, okay?
Don't!
Don't go... Mom... Dad...
Don't go... Stay here...
It's all my fault...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
In order to kidnap you, the child prodigy,
your parents were murdered,
and your sister was caught up
in the whole mess.
The loss of your loved ones
robbed you of your emotions,
and that fixation of yours shifted
from your parents to your sister, but...
Why...
Why are you doing this, Sis?
I hate it!
I hate you, Sis!
And I don't want this bell!
Soon, you were rejected by your sister,
and the only thing left for you
was the life of an assassin.
In order to survive, you continued to kill,
and before you knew it,
you were living only to kill.
You became the world's most fearsome assassin.
Welcome home, Xue. My beloved disciple.
...Yuki...
Ms. Yuki!
Are you okay?
Oh... Master Hitoyoshi...
Sorry for just barging in.
Something didn't seem right earlier,
so I came to check on you, but...
You were groaning a lot in your sleep.
Are you okay?
U-Um, M-Ms. Yuki...
I fully understand that
I may be troubling you, but...
Right now...
Please let me stay this way,
if only for a moment.
Ms. Yuki?
Did you have another nightmare?
You could call it a nightmare...
but it was also something more.
A dream of a distant time long past...
I'm sorry. I can't remember anything.
I see.
You know how babies stop crying
when patted on the back?
I heard that the patting sound
is similar to a mother's heartbeat,
which calms them down.
I'm just repeating what
my mom told me, though.
Master Hitoyoshi's heartbeat...
It's so soothing.
Ogiso Private High School
Science Room
What?!
Yuki, you don't know anything
about the Katsuda Festival?
That's right. I figured from the name
it was something festive, but...
Correct!
Its official name is the
Katsuda Grand Triple Festival!
Champion
It's a sports festival, cultural festival, and music festival all in one—
the Katsuda Festival for short.
Katsuda Festival
It's a long-standing tradition
here at Ogiso High!
Each class participates in the three festivals
and competes in an overall ranking.
One of the prizes given to the winning class
is a specially made Premium Katsuda's Sauce.
PKS for short.
That's gotta be tough for Ms. Yuki
to hear in her sauce-deprived state!
Well, it's impossible for sophomores
to win the Katsuda Festival
without knowing the ins and outs.
The student council president's
class is bound to win.
If we're aiming for the top, we can't afford
to lose at the upcoming cultural festival!
We have to keep up with our grades, too.
Grades, too?
Yeah. How did you do on the test, Ms. Yuki?
I managed not to fail!
That's a nice smile.
I was hoping to avoid supplementary
lessons, at the very least.
I'm glad you didn't fail.
That would affect your standing
for the Katsuda Festival.
Standing?
First Semester End Results
+ Sports Festival Score
+
Second Semester End Results +
Cultural Festival Tournament Rank
+ Store Profits
+
Third Semester End Results
+ Music Festival Evaluation
=
Class with Highest Overall
Score Is the Winner
As you can see, the average score of the class
contributes to the overall ranking
for the Katsuda Festival.
I think our class average was about 60 percent?
If you get below a 37,
you won't be eligible to participate!
Ogiso Private High School
Sophomore Chemistry
Name
Yuki Yokoya
So for someone like me who's below average...
Oh, wh-what should I do?
I-It'll be okay! As long as you
can maintain a passing grade,
you won't be so far behind,
and you'll still be able to participate.
Those with low test scores
just have to work extra hard!
Work extra hard...
I will work extra hard!
It seems last year, they did
a big trivia competition.
I wonder what it'll be this year.
Katsuda Bread's in short supply right now,
so I had a hell of a hard time
getting some today.
It wouldn't kill you to show
some gratitude, you sauce junkie.
Yes, I am grateful.
Thank you, Grace.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
Did she forget that I took Hitoyoshi
hostage not that long ago?
Or does she just not see me
as a threat at all?
If we're done, hurry up and get outta here.
Name
Yui Ishii
If I get caught doing this kind of stuff,
I'll be in hot water.
Oh, come on.
This isn't some black market trade.
Anyway, get out of here!
I have to finish grading these tests
before gym class in fifth period.
Master Hitoyoshi, regarding the
Katsuda Festival from earlier...
What kind of results would we need to
achieve in order for our class to win?
A-Are you seriously aiming to win?
Well, I guess given your abilities
it might be possible, but...
We need to keep your true identity
hidden at the same time.
Oh, you planning to compete
in the Katsuda Festival, Yuki?
You know you handed in your gym class
written exam without your name on it, right?
If you fail, you can't compete.
During the test, I took a peek
at your answer sheet,
and noticed yours was the
only one without a name.
Ogiso Private High School
Sophomore Health and Physical Education
Name
So this one has to be yours, right?
Well, that's a real shame.
You would've passed, too.
Well, you get an A+ in physical ability, so it
shouldn't affect your grades proper, but...
I was a fool to be grateful
to someone like you...
Don't give me that!
You have only yourself to blame here!
Um... Would it be possible for you
to allow her to write her name in now?
Hold up!
You really think I'm gonna cut you
such a sweet deal for free?
She's the worst!
I'll let you get out of flunking the exam...
if you do a job for me.
Don't worry. I won't ask you to kill anyone.
And of course, I'll be terminating
our Katsuda Bread deal, as well.
Also, one more condition.
When you go to a ramen joint,
you gotta leave the sauce at home!
You're still stewing on that?!
I suppose sacrifices must be made...
Wait, Ms. Yuki!
You can't give in to her coercive tactics!
Hm?
Wind?
Name
Yuki Yokoya
What? Her name is filled in?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What kind of magic trick was that?!
Oh, that was...
Hold on a second, Ms. Yuki.
It's clear to me now that Ms. Grace
was simply mistaken to begin with.
We could even say she was seeing things.
Your name was already on
the paper from the start.
I see you're starting to grow a spine, too.
All right.
I'll let you go this time,
but I won't be so lenient in future!
You got that, sauce junkie?!
I hate to put it like this,
but Ms. Grace is pretty easy—
I heard that, Hitoyoshi!
I'm sorry.
So, how did you do it, Ms. Yuki?
Well, that was...
I hope I was able to be
of some use to Ms. Yuki.
Yes. You were very helpful.
Thank you very much.
Um...
You're in our class, aren't you?
Um... Um...
Oh, Ms. Hikage?
Uh...
Oh... Um... I... I'm...
I'm Naka Hikage.
And...
I know a way we can win the Cultural Festival!